The story of a child… and his son.
That's My Boy is a comedy film directed by Sean Anders.
While in his teens, Donny fathered a son, Todd, and raised him as
a single parent up until Todd's 18th birthday.
Now, after not seeing each other for years, Todd's world comes crashing
down when Donny resurfaces just before Todd's wedding.
Donny Berger, played by Adam Sandler.
Todd Peterson, played by Andy Samberg.
Jamie Martin, played by Leighton Meester.
Vanilla Ice, played by Vanilla Ice.
Steve Spirou, played by Tony Orlando.
Phil, played by Will Forte.
That's My Boy is a 2012 American comedy film directed by Sean Anders, written by David Caspe,
and produced by Adam Sandler, Jack Giarraputo, Heather Parry, and Allen Covert.
It stars Sandler and Andy Samberg, with Leighton Meester and James Caan.
It also stars Vanilla Ice, Tony Orlando, Will Forte, Milo
Ventimiglia, and Susan Sarandon in supporting roles.
The film follows Donny Berger (Sandler), a middle-aged alcoholic who once enjoyed celebrity status for being at the center of a teacher-student statutory rape case, as he tries to rekindle his relationship with his adult
son, Todd Peterson/Han Solo Berger (Samberg), born as the result of that illicit relationship, in hopes that their televised reunion will earn him enough money to avoid going to prison for his tax debts.
Produced by Sandler's Happy Madison Productions in association with Relativity Media, That's My Boy was released in the United States on June 15, 2012, by Columbia
Pictures, to a critical and commercial failure, grossing only $57.7 million against a $57.5–70 million budget and was negatively reviewed by critics.
The film explores themes of talk show, older woman seduces
younger guy, women's prison, strip club, drinking.
The tone is lighthearted.